# Mo Zhai

150 E Schiller Street Elmhurst IL 60126

Phone: (773)678-3620 Web: <u>www.zhaimobile.com</u> E-mail: mozhai@live.com

#### Me

I am an experienced software engineer with 3 years of professional experience. My experience covers development using Objective C, Java, .NET, C++, Javascript, and many other languages on top of most popular frameworks. I have delivered several enterprise web applications as well as mobile apps for business in both iOS App Store and Android Play Store. I am a hard worker with great learning skills, have enthusiastic heart for IT industry.

#### Skills

- Frameworks: iOS, Android, Liferay, ASP.Net MVC, J2EE, Dojo, Lucene.Net, OpenGL
- Language: Objective C, Java, JavaScript, C++, C#, Python, SQL
- IDE: Visual Studio, Xcode, Eclipse, and etc.
- Tools: Bazaar, Git, JIRA, Unity3D
- Platforms: MacOS X, Windows, Linux

#### Experience

Full Stack Software Engineer @ Echelon Consulting, L.L.C.

5/2012 - now

- Developing core financial web applications for global business using ASP.Net MVC.
- Implemented the main iOS and Android apps (front-end and back-end) for A large law firm with more than 1,800 employees in 19 offices worldwide.
- Upgraded the company web site for a global management consulting firm using Liferay.
- Built auto-translation, searching, and server tools for top business.

**Software developer internships**@ Space to Play

2/2012 - 4/2012

• Accomplished a 3Ds Max plug-in in C++, which facilitates editing and visualization of urban 3D building models from geo-spatial database (PostGIS).

Graduate Assistant and Tech support @ CDM, DePaul University

01/2011 - 03/2012

- Maintained and managed network, server and other equipments for labs.
- Operated software deployment and testing for classes and events.

Network Engineer @ China TieTong- Equipment Center

08/2007 - 03/2009

- Analyzed, and refined the central node of the company PSTN network.
- Tool development for a multiple million equipment upgrading project.

## **Education** DePaul University

Graduation March, 2012

Master of Science in **Computer Game Development**, Graduate School of College of Computing and Digital Media GPA=3.98

### Tianjin Normal University

Graduation July, 2007

Bachelor's degree in **Computer Engineering**, emphasis on Information Engineering GPA=3.21 First rank scholarship